

ANNA LIN

VANCOUVER, BC

+1 (778) 522-8701 # ANNALIN.WORK@GMAIL.COM # HTTPS://CETACEALIN.GITHUB.IO

Summary

3rd year UBC student pursing a Bachelor of Arts in Mathematics with experience in software development and quality assurance from academia and web application development. Experienced in tracking project status and bugs through JIRA, breaking down projects into deliverables and coding/testing said deliverables for my web applications. Experienced in running UI tests (Selenium) to assert web elements are present and performing actions for basic sanity testing. Please see https://cetacealin.github.io for portfolio and demos.

Skill Highlights

- Automation (Selenium) & Unit Testing
- Java, React, JavaScript, HTML/CSS, Express.js
- Data Structures and Algorithms
- MySQL, NoSQL, AWS, Google Cloud

Projects

Social – A social media website for users to post, like and comment

- Onboarded Firebase authentication for user registration and user authentication
- Created REST APIs for signup, login, user actions, post actions with Firebase Cloud Functions
- Created database schema for users and posts and integrated it to Google FireStore
- Created Social frontend for sign in, timeline, posting and user profile with React

Online Chatroom – A chatroom website where users can join & send messages

- Onboarded WebSocket API from API Gateway to deliver chat messages over WebSocket
- Created a Lambda for handling connecting, disconnecting, sending private & public messages
- Created Online Chatroom frontend to provide interface for users to join & chat with React

To Do List – A to do list website for users to create tasks or delete them

Created To Do List frontend to provide interface to create tasks or delete them with React

Personal Portfolio

A static page hosted on GitHub with my portfolio built using HTML, CSS & JavaScript

Education

Bachelor of Arts – Pursuing Mathematics Major – 09/2019 to present **University of British Columbia, Vancouver, BC**

- CPSC103 Introduction to Systematic Program Design
- CPSC110 Computation, Programs, and Programming
- CPSC221 Basic Algorithms and Data Structures
- CPSC213 Introduction to Computer Systems

Previous Experience

Receptionist, Audi, Richmond, BC – 12/2020 to 03/2021 Stylist, AllSaints, Richmond, BC – 09/2019 to 01/2021